Guide to the Ron Kolm Papers, 1970-2016 MSS.079
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VI: Announcements, 13847
  - Subseries B: Gallery Show Announcements, 13848
    - Collins & Millazzo Gallery, undated; 13900 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Costan, Chris, undated; 13899 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Crumb, R, undated; 13898 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Dali, Salvador, undated; 13897 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Drooker, Eric, undated; 13896 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Ecker, Ken, undated; 13895 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Exit Art, undated; 13894 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Fachetti Galleries, undated; 13893 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Fine, Larry, undated; 13892 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Finley, Karen, undated; 13891 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Folzenlogen, Tim, undated; 13890 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Friedman, Drew, undated; 13889 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Gosfield, Josh, undated; 13888 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Gracie Mansion Gallery, undated; 13887 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Grooms, Red, undated; 13886 (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Gross, Mimi, undated; 13885 (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - Hamburger, Sydney, undated; 13884 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Helio Galleries, undated; 13883 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Heller, Neddi, undated; 13882 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Himmelstein, Shelley, undated; 13881 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Holness, Victor, undated; 13880 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Isaac, Jeffrey, undated; 13879 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Jensen, Bill, undated; 13878 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Jernigan, Candy, undated; 13877 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Kaufman, Betsy, undated; 13876 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Kostabi, Mark, undated; 13875 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Kostelanetz, Richard, undated; 13874 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Kruth, John, undated; 13873 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Madore, Michael, undated; 13872 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Malanga, Gerard, undated; 13871 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Miller, John, undated; 13870 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Nechvatal, Joseph, undated; 13869 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Ochiishi, undated; 13868 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Palaia, Franc, undated; 13867 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Public Illumination Gallery, undated; 13866 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Raveson, Art, undated; 13865 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Sandlin, David, undated; 13864 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Sharpe Gallery, undated; 13863 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Sides, Wayne, undated; 13862 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Spiegelman, Art, undated; 13861 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Stevenson, Patrick, undated; 13860 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Tisa, Ken, undated; 13859 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Tompkins, Betty, undated; 13858 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Turyn, Anne, undated; 13857 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Ward-Nasse Gallery, undated; 13856 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - White Columns Gallery, undated; 13855 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Wilson, Blair, undated; 13854 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Witz, Robert, undated; 13853 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Wojnarowicz, David, undated; 13852 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Zelevansky, Paul, undated; 13851 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Miscellaneous Gallery Announcements, undated; 13850 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Group Shows, undated; 13849 (Box 10, Folder 36)
- Series VII: Sound recordings, 13807
  This series consists of sound recordings and video recordings on various formats, and includes poetry, music, and spoken word recordings.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
  - Anthony, Bill -- Slide Show. Audiotape Cassette, undated; 13846 (Box 29)
  - Batteries Not Included. Audiotape Cassette, undated; 13845 (Box 29)
  - Best Wishes To Rank. Audiotape Cassette, undated; 13844 (Box 29)
  - Blagg, Max--Five Days, (Fez), 4/21/93. Audiotape Cassette, 1993; 13843 (Box 29)
  - Blagg, Max -- Monkey Wrench, etc., The Other Gallery, 2/1/90 Audiotape Cassette, 1990; 13842 (Box 29)
  - Blagg, Max -- 10/28/87. Audiotape Cassette, 1987; 13841 (Box 29)
  - Cherches, Peter -- Sonorexia, w/ Elliott Sharpe & others. Audiotape Cassette, undated; 13840 (Box 29)
  - Cherches, Peter -- Videotape, w/ Lee Feldman 11/7/86, 1986; 13839 (Box 29)
  - Fishberg, Lawrence -- 10 Songs in only a little over 15 minutes, 1995. Audiotape Cassette, 13838 (Box 29)
  - Fugs, The -- Keeping The Issues Alive, Ed Sanders, Tuli Kupferberg, others 1984. Audiotape Cassette, 13837 (Box 29)
  - In-Cafe Cool -- Cups. Loudon Wainright, others n.d. Compact Disc, undated; 13836 (Box 29)
  - Just Say Ho -- audiotape cassette, undated; 13835 (Box 29)
  - Holman, Bob -- Panic DJ. Audiotape Cassette, undated; 13834 (Box 29)
  - Kolm, Ron - 11/15/86. Audiotape Cassette, 1986; 13833 (Box 29)
  - Kolm, Ron -- Nuyorican Poets Cafe 3/24/90. Audiotape Cassette, 1990; 13832 (Box 29)
  - Kolm, Ron -- Ridge St. Gallery Reading, w/Hal Sirowitz 11/14/87. Audiotape Cassette, 1987; 13831 (Box 29)
  - Kolm, Ron -- Songs (by Fishberg,) 1995. Audiotape Cassette, 13830 (Box 29)
  - Kolm, Ron -- Swimming At The Shallow End Of The Pool, 1995 (2 copies) Audiotape Cassettes, 13829 (Box 29)
  - Kruth, John -- Midnight Snack. Compact Disc, undated; 13828 (Box 29)
  - Kupferberg, Tuli -- Seance Piece. "Tuli Channels Marx" 3/29/94 Audiotape Cassette, 1994; 13827 (Box 29)
  - Kupferberg, Tuli -- Tuli & Friends. Audiotape Cassette, undated; 13826 (Box 29)
  - Mellow Freakin' Woodies-- Mellow Freakin' Mood. 1992. Audiotape Cassette, 13825 (Box 29)
  - Merry Christmas The North Pole Bull Shit, 1986 (?) Audiotape Cassette, 13824 (Box 29)
  - Nuyorican Symphony -- 100 poets including. Bob Holman, Carolyn Peyser, Eileen Myles, Carl Watson, Edwin Torres, Miguel Algarin, Ron Kolm, Sparrow, Sapphire, etc. 1992, Compact Disc, 13823 (Box 29)
  - Plantenga, Bart - Avec "After he vomited, Bart sat on a rock." Audiotape Cassette, undated; 13822 (Box 29)
  - Plantenga, Bart -- Greetings From Home Of Freedom. Audiotape Cassette, undated; 13821 (Box 29)
  - Plantenga, Bart -- Mr. Valbar May Just Have Won Five Million Dollars - Audiotape Cassette, undated; 13820 (Box 29)
  - Plantenga, Bart -- Poetry As Healer. Audiotape Cassette, undated; 13819 (Box 29)
  - Plantenga, Bart -- Word Is The Bird. AH - OOO. Sperm motility, etc. Audiotape Cassette, undated; 13818 (Box 29)
  - Silent Not -- audiotape cassette & tattoo, undated; 13817 (Box 29)
  - Sirowitz, Hal -- Idiodyssey, 1993. w/Lawrence Fishberg. Audiotape Cassette, 13816 (Box 29)
  - Sparrow -- May I Take A Bath, (Foamola), 1992. Audiotape Cassette, 13815 (Box 29)
  - Sparrow -- Spit On The Dishes (Foamola), 1993. Audiotape Cassette, 13814 (Box 29)
  - Unbearables At Fales -- NYU 5/7/96. Videotape, 1996; 13813 (Box 29)
  - Unbearable Beatniks Of Life --The Poetry Project, 2/22/93 Tape 1: Max Blagg, Michael Carter, Jim Feast, David Ulin, Jill Rapaport, Ron Kolm, Sharon Mesmer, Bart Plantenga Audiotape Cassette, 1993; 13812 (Box 29)
  - Unbearable Beatniks Of Life -- The Poetry Project 2/22/93 Tape 2: Bart Plantenga, Jim Feast, Deborah Pintonelli, Hal Sirowitz, Jill Rapaport. Audiotape Cassette, 1993; 13811 (Box 29)
  - What Makes A Poem Great? --audiotape cassette, undated; 13810 (Box 29)
  - Wild Words -- Cups Records. William Burroughs, Hal Sirowitz, Charles Bukowski, Harvey Fierstein, Paul Bowles, Hakim Bey (a.k.a. Peter Lamborn Wilson), Bob Holman, and others. Compact Disc, undated; 13809 (Box 29)
  - Wilson, Peter Lamborn -- T.A.Z. Hakim Bey. Compact Disc, undated; 13808 (Box 29)
- Series VIII: Original Art, 13781
  This series contains a small collection of original art works by downtown artists.
  - Adams, Jeffrey--3 originals for "Back Fence" readings, undated; 13806 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Appearances # 17: "Suburban Ambush" issue. Original art Works by: Ken Brown, Jorga Cardin, Ken Tisa, & other unsigned. 8 pieces total, undated; 13805 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Big Fish Magazine-- "No Words" Issue-- Original Art. Unsigned, undated; 13804 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Brown, Ken -- 2 "Wrap City Sheets", undated; 13802 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Cardin, Jorga --9 works, 2 of them oversized, undated; 13801 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - CAREN, Original for Poetry Reading announcement on an aerogramme + 1 copy, undated; 13800 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Deyab, Larry-- 6 cards and one "work on paper", undated; 13799 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Drooker, Eric-- 4 works, undated; 13798 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Hell is where everything faces the ground. Unsigned. #NAME?, undated; 13797 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Hutchinson, Bruce-- 12 black and white works on cardstock + accompanying envelope, undated; 13796 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Isaac, Jeffrey--3 originals for poetry reading announcements, undated; 13795 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Kolm, Ron, 261355 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Kostabi, Mark --1 original art for a poetry reading announcement for reading by Richard Bandanza, Ron Kolm, & Carmelita Tropicana at the St. Mark's Poetry Project "March 17th" no year cited, undated; 13794 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Madore, Michael -- 1 original art for a poetry reading announcement at "Back Fence" by Samuel Menashe, Michael LaBombarda, and Thomas McGonigle, undated; 13793 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Moisan, Jim -- 2 originals of reading announcement for Low Tech Press, undated; 13792 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Randall, Michael --33 drawings, undated; 13791 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Raveson, Art--4 originals for poetry reading announcements, undated; 13790 (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Spiegelman, Art -- 1 limited black and white print with accompanying letter from Random House, Inc, undated; 13789 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Spiegelman, Art-1 chromolithograph from "The Wild Party" Signed and Framed, undated; 13788 (Box 1, Folder 18A)
  - Stevenson, Patrick -- 39 works. Including black & white drawings, 1 color work, for calendars, reading announcements, etc, undated; 13786 (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Witz, Bob -- 1 black and white drawing, possibly of Allen Ginsberg, with blue pen marks over face, undated; 13785 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Zummer, Thomas -- Zummer file #1 Color and black and white works. 87 pages, undated; 13784 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Zummer, Thomas -- Zummer file #2 94 pages, including the series: "Tales Of Drama and Inconvenience," "Brain Dead Dog," "Tales From Zummerville", undated; 13783 (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Zummer, Thomas -- Zummer file # 3 5 works on paper, in color 1 work on paper, black and white, 1 color card with the words "you're right it's the wise men and they've got them pointed right at us", undated; 13782 (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Zummer, Thomas -- Zummer #4 Art, 261356 (Box 10, Folder 60)
- Series IX: Ephemera, 13762
  This series contains ephemeral objects, and includes Keith Haring pins, matchbook poems, pencil poems, stamp art, sticker art, sticker poems, and a ping pong ball announcement from CBGB's, amongst other like items.
  - R. Crumb Trading Cards, undated; 13780 (Box 11)
  - Artkards 1992 Series, 13779 (Box 11)
  - Heroes of the Blues Cards, undated; 13778 (Box 11)
  - Crackpots & Visionaries Vol. 2 Cards, David Sandlin, artist, undated; 13777 (Box 11)
  - Early Jazz Greats Cards, undated; 13776 (Box 11)
  - RAW buttons (in a round, plastic container), undated; 13775 (Box 11)
  - 3 Pencils by Beth Lapides. (Actual pencils.), undated; 13774 (Box 11)
  - 6 Matchbooks (w. poem by Ron Kolm), undated; 13773 (Box 11)
  - 1 button by William Anthony, undated; 13772 (Box 11)
  - 1 matchbook called SUN/NIGHT w. poem by James Pelletier, undated; 13771 (Box 11)
  - 1 Charles Bukowski/Black Sparrow button, undated; 13770 (Box 11)
  - 1 button from Coalition To Stop U.S. Intervention In The Middle East, undated; 13769 (Box 11)
  - WFMU by Kaz, undated; 13768 (Box 11)
  - The Product Is You Sticker, with text by William Burroughs Ragged Edge Press, undated; 13767 (Box 11)
  - Art Spiegelman Cards, undated; 13766 (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Janet Restino Cards, undated; 13765 (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - RAW #1 Cards, undated; 13764 (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Miscellaneous Printed Ephemera (Business Cards, Bookmarks, etc.), undated; 13763 (Box 10, Folder 64)
- Series X: Low Tech Press, 13746
  This series consists of production Files for Low Tech Press, Ron Kolm's small press.
  - The Catering Hall, undated; 13761 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Famous French Poets, undated; 13760 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Girlie Pictures (oversized), undated; 13759 (Box 1, Folder 2A)
  - Low Tech, undated; 13758 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Low Tech Manual, undated; 13757 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Low Tech Press, undated; 13756 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Monkey by Max Blagg (oversized), undated; 13755 (Box 1, Folder 5A)
  - Suburban Ambush, undated; 13754 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Welcome To The Barbecue, undated; 13753 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Welcome To The Barbecue, undated; 13752 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Welcome To The Barbecue--2nd Edition Corrections, undated; 13751 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Welcome To The Barbecue--3rd Edition--4th Edition, undated; 13750 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Welcome To The Barbecue--5th Edition, undated; 13749 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous Receipts & Tax Records, undated; 13748 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Zummer, Tom--"Make Love Not War" w. Ron Kolm (oversized), undated; 13747 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Series XI: Posters, 13735
  This series contains posters Kolm collected from the downtown scene. Included are posters for the Sex Pistols as well as posters for many downtown books, such as Raw magazine, and a variety of signed prints by downtown artists.
  - Art: Bill Anthony, undated; 13745 (Folder 3 Left)
  - Art: David Sandlin, undated; 13744 (Folder 20)
  - Galleries & Artists, undated; 13743 (Folder 2 Left)
  - Literature. Miscellaneous, undated; 13742 (Folder 5 Left)
  - Magazines, Readings; Mickey Mao by Ken Brown, undated; 13741 (Folder 1 Left)
  - RAW Magazine, undated; 13739 (Folder 7 Left)
  - Unbearables, undated; 13738 (Folder 21)
  - Performances, undated; 13737 (Folder 6 Left)
  - St. Mark's Poetry Project, undated; 13736 (Folder 14 Right)
  - Poodle with a Mohawk, undated; 263525 (Folder 13 Right)
  - Sex Pistols "Fuck Forever" (1986), undated; 263526 (Folder 18)
- Series XII: Catalogs, 13699
  This series consists of catalogues from small and independent presses, and consortia who published downtown works.
  - Amok Press, undated; 13734 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Anti Catalog, undated; 13733 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Art Market Catalogue, undated; 13732 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Assembling Press Publications, undated; 13731 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Autonomedia, undated; 13730 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Black Ice Books, undated; 13729 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Black Sparrow Press, undated; 13728 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Blast Books, undated; 13727 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - City Lights Publishers, undated; 13726 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Dalkey Archives Press, undated; 13725 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Burning Deck Books, undated; 13724 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Four Walls/Eight Windows, undated; 13723 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Garden Street Press, undated; 13722 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Generations Unlimited, undated; 13721 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Giorno Poetry Systems, undated; 13720 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Granary Books, undated; 13719 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Hanging Loose Press, undated; 13718 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Hanuman Books, undated; 13717 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - High Risk/Serpent's Tail Books, undated; 13716 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Jargon Society, undated; 13715 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Kitchen Sink, undated; 13714 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - New York Small Press Association, undated; 13713 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Photography In New York, undated; 13712 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Printed Matter, Inc (1 of 2), undated; 13711 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Printed Matter (2 of 2), 233508 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - RAW, undated; 13710 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Red Dust, undated; 13709 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Riverside Writers Group, undated; 13708 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Seven Stories Press, undated; 13707 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Small Press Distribution, undated; 13706 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Tanam Press, undated; 13705 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Teachers & Writers Collaborative, undated; 13704 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Tellus, undated; 13703 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Thin Air Video, undated; 13702 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Weighed Anchor Press, undated; 13701 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - WFMU "Curiosities Catalogs", undated; 13700 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Series XIV: Periodicals, 13617
  This series contains periodicals important to, featuring or produced by members of the downtown scene.
  - Benderson, Bruce "Goodbye Sleaze, Hello Disneyland," Cups magazine, #73, p. 9, undated; 13688 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Cantsin, Monty, interview. The Neoist Conspiracy. Ipso Facto Magazine, # 4 Spring 1988., pp. 22-25, 13687 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Cherches, Peter "Lift your right arm, she said." From Bagatelles. High Times magazine, March, 1982., p. 10, 13686 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Cherches, Peter. Tales Of Ordinary Madness. Lightworks magazine, Number 18, Winter 1986-87. pp. 4 -- 10, 1986-1987; 13685 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Davies, Bevan -- "Photographs" Genesis: Grasp, Vol. 1, #2. 1969. pp. 16 - 21, 13684 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Eidus, Janice -- "Nautilus" Spec. magazine. n.d. pp. 50-53, undated; 13683 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Eidus, Janice -- Interview, Cups magazine, p. 28, undated; 13682 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Hardin, Rob -- 2 poems, Java Journal, Vol. 1, #8, November 1994. p. 10, 13681 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Haring, Keith -- Review of Haring's Journals, Rain Taxi magazine, p47, undated; 13680 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Holland, Barbara -- The Grendhal Poetry Review, #1., 1986. Six poems, 13679 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Kolm, Ron -- Low Tech Press quote. Writer's Digest magazine. Jun-84. p. 46, 1984; 13678 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Kolm, Ron -- Review of "Welcome To The Barbecue" Contact II, Summer 1982. p. 5, 13677 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Kolm, Ron -- "Suburban Ambush" (poem)., The Peabody Review #2, 1990. p. 19, 13676 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Kolm, Ron -- "Suburban Ambush" (poem), Heat #15, June 1985. Thirdm unnumbered page, 13675 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Kolm, Ron -- Photo of Ron Kolm, High Times magazine, July 1981. p. 67, 13674 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Kolm, Ron -- "Suburban Ambush" (poem) International Poetry Review, #2 October 1986. Unnumbered pages, 13673 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Kolm, Ron -- "Suburban Ambush" (poem) Sheep magazine. Feb-84. p. 62, 1984; 13672 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Kolm, Ron -- 2 poems. Arulo magazine. Volume #21, December 1982. pp. 14, 52, 13671 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Kolm, Ron -- "Self Help" text. Image: David Sandlin., Chemical Imbalance magazine, Vol. 2 #1, 1989. p. 100. Record included w. magazine, 13670 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Kolm, Ron -- The Poetry Project Newsletter, #92. Oct-82. Ad for Low Tech Press, inside back cover, 1982; 13669 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Kostabi, Mark -- 2 drawings. Rio magazine. Fall 1987. Unnumbered pages, 13668 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Kostelanetz, Richard -- "Why Audio Drama Now?" Theater X magazine, 1986. p. 9, 13667 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - LaBombarda, Michael -- 2 poems, Samisdat magazine, Vol. IV, #4, Summer 1975. pp. 17, 18, 13666 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - LaBombarda, Michael -- "Poets Don't Lose Gunfights With The Moon" (poem) Source magazine, Vol. 2, #1, 1977. p. 11, 13665 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - McGrath, Patrick -- "Enter The Strange Realm Of Patrick McGrath," by Sean Abbott, "Mad Love In The Garden" by Patrick McGrath, p. 2l At Random, magazine. Random House, Inc. Winter, 1997, 13664 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Plantenga, Bart -- "Confessions Of A Beer Mystic", Big Dick Review, Volume 0, #1, Spring 1989. p. 1, 13663 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Plantenga, Bart -- "soon" (poem) Police Beat magazine #1, Spring, 1980. pp. 60-6l, 13662 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Plantenga, Bart -- "Melon Rinds We Have Eaten" (poem), Generation magazine, Volume XXVI, #1, 1975, 13661 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Plantenga, Bart -- "Paris Scratch" Prose. Joe Soap's Canoe magazine, 1992. unnumbered pages, 13660 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Plantenga, Bart -- "Rhomboyd" The Nice Review, p. 14. Pages upside down, undated; 13659 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Plantenga, Bart -- 9 works. Carsick magazine. 1977, pp. 3, 4, 7, 8, 15, 17, 23, 27, 34, 38, 13658 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Plantenga, Bart -- 6 works, The Art Of Darkness Magazine, 1978?, 13657 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Plantenga, Bart -- "knew the tropic", Roadwerk magazine, #IV, 1984, 13656 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Plantenga, Bart -- "Really living: Adventures In Truth II" Yellow Silk magazine, #13, Winter 1984, p. 19, 13655 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Plantenga, Bart -- "Fellow De Se", Sandbox magazine #3, 1995. p. 14, 13654 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Plantenga, Bart -- Review of "Wiggling Wishbone" by Bart Plantenga. Paramour magazine, Vol. 2, #3 p. 26, undated; 13653 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Sandlin, David -- "Sinland" Art? magazine, 1996, pp. 30-35, 13652 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Schiffrin, Anya -- "Panorama Literaria U.S.A" Ajoblanco magazine, 1987. pp. 90-91, 13651 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Schiffrin, Anya -- "Los Yuppies Asaltan El East Village" Ajoblanco magazine, 1988, pp. 56 -- 63, 13650 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Siegle, Robert -- Ad for "Suburban Ambush" anthology by Ron Kolm & Robert Siegle. Granta magazine #28, 1989, 13649 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Sirowitz, Hal -- 2 poems, Realities #3, broadside, 1985, 13648 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Sirowitz, Hal, "A Bullet Doesn't Stop At Flesh" Lusty Mover magazine, January 93, p. 12, 1993; 13647 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Sirowitz, Hal -- "These Are My Parents And This Is My Girl", (prose) Croton Review, magazine, 1985, pp. 49 - 51, 13646 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Sirowitz, Hal -- "Bumping Into An Ex- Lover," Lucky Star magazine, vol. 2, #3, October 1985, p. 11, 13645 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Sirowitz, Hal -- 19 poems, Newsletter Inago, July 1986, 13644 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Sirowitz, Hal -- "Submerging" attached to Bogg 53. Broadside. or ad, undated; 13643 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Sirowitz, Hal -- "Pay Me A Visit", Without Halos magazine, Vol. 3, 1985. p. 4, 13642 (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Sirowitz, Hal -- 2 poems, The Bare Foot Review, vol. 2, #1, 1989. pp. 15,16, 13641 (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Sirowitz, Hal -- Announcement for "Girlie Pictures", Hanging Loose magazine, #43, Winter 1982-1983. p. 36, 13640 (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Sirowitz, Hal -- "Designing Women's Clothes," Abraxas magazine 27/28. p. 43. Review of "Girlie Pictures" p. 59, undated; 13639 (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - Sirowitz, Hal -- "Beginnings Are Important to Me," fiction, Writ magazine, #17, 1985, 13638 (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Sirowitz, Hal -- "Death Gift" High Times magazine, January 1983. p. 9, 13637 (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - Sirowitz, Hal -- 2 poems. Wu Wei magazine, #8, unnumbered pages. n.d, undated; 13636 (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - Sirowitz, Hal -- "The Sitting Dance," Poetry Motel magazine, #5, 1985, p.12, 13635 (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - Sirowitz, Hal --"She Got Paint All Over Her Robe," Greens magazine, p. 40, undated; 13634 (Box 14, Folder 55)
  - Sirowitz, Hal -- "A Strange Man Was Breathing On My Phone," Folio magazine, Spring 1985, p. 9, 13633 (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - Sirowitz, Hal -- "Money, Money" Sonoma Mandala magazine Vol. 12. 1985 pp.64-65, 13632 (Box 14, Folder 57)
  - Sparrow -- "Talk Of The Town" Machete magazine, #1, 1994, p. 38, 13631 (Box 14, Folder 58)
  - Spiegelman, Art -- "The Wild Party", drawings, The New Yorker magazine, June/July 1994, pp. 155-163, 13630 (Box 14, Folder 59)
  - Sukenick, Ronald -- "The Underground Exposed", Cups magazine, June 1996. pp. 14-Dec, 13629 (Box 14, Folder 60)
  - Tillman, Lynne -- Interview. Cups magazine, #69 p. 24. Interview by Rob Hardin, undated; 13628 (Box 14, Folder 61)
  - Unbearables -- "the Unbearables" by Donna Romanazzi, Endangered Species magazine, vol. 2, #1 p. 38, undated; 13627 (Box 14, Folder 62)
  - Unbearables review -- Unsigned review, The Review of Contemporary Fiction, Spring 1996, p. 169, 13626 (Box 14, Folder 63)